Subscribe to the bankbajar.com
channel and press the bell button
to watch the video first Hello friends,
welcome to our YouTube channel
bankbajar.com Friends, if you have an
account in IDFC Bank, then watch this video
carefully. In this video, we will
tell you important information related to it.
Friends, if you
want to avail this offer, then
download the mobile application on your mobile and its link is
given in the description. You can go from here and
activate this application and login.
As soon as you log in,
you will see an option on its home page, you will
click on subscribe and your next page will
open where you will see that the
offer for personal loan on credit card will be shown to you,
like in mine, it is showing an offer of 90, we will
now reject it and
as soon as we click on the next topic, it will
open on our next page where it will
ask for the amount at the top. So friends, the
amount we got in this is 90 maximum, so we can click here
Many people apply for 9000, that too
for 12 months, so we will enter 9000 here
and select the month for how many months we
want, so we have 12 here and click next
and see here the rate of interest is
showing 15.49, one percent processing
fee is showing, after this we will
calculate it and see at the bottom
your MI is also showing, here you have to
pay 845 rupees MI and you will check all the details here,
after this you will click on the terms and conditions
pick below and remove the availability and
as soon as you do this you will immediately
receive an SMS here that you have
successfully applied for the loan, just
after that you will immediately receive another SMS
which will inform you that the balance has been credited to your account,
now see here the total
available balance is also showing and
here my balance has come, friends if
you liked this video then like this video
and subscribe to this channel
friends if you also
want to apply for a loan  Or if you
want any information from us, you can comment on us
or you can also mail us on our mail id,
we will definitely reply to your comment
and friends, do subscribe to this channel
because on this
we keep giving important information related to your account.